Marching to the New Wonderland
An Unexpected Disaster
How many times have I told you, Paddi?
Don’t eat while driving.
You need to focus on the road.
I’ve still got a stash.
I knew it.
If you ever eat and drive again, I’ll throw it all out.
No!
It’s a sweet-tooth aphid!
No, you can’t have this one.
Don’t eat my candy!
Weslie!
I’m coming down to get you!
Hi there, little goats.
Oh no.
The Energy Seed is mine at last.
Wolnie and I can stay young forever.
Oh, come on!
I’m definitely not telling you
that Weslie fell out of the train and got dragged away by an aphid.
Please stop talking, Paddi.
Oh, I see! I’ll go find him right away.
Good thing I didn’t tell him
that the safe box’s locks are time-sensitive.
If the prints turn dark,
that means it needs the handprints again.
Oh, I see!
Then I’ll take the Energy Seed with me,
and I’ll make Weslie open the lock as soon as I find him.
Justice Spider, take the goats back to Sirius
and keep an eye on them.
Roger that.
Give back my lollipop!
There you are.
Wolffy?
The Energy Seed? Where did you get that from?
Mm-hm. Your handprint is all that’s left.
Give me your hand right now!
Here comes a honey fruit!
Here comes another one!
Open the Energy Seed box.
No.
Yes!
No!
While he’s asleep, I’ll count down from three,
and we’ll run in five separate directions
so he won’t be able to catch us.
Are we ready?
Three, two, one.
Trying to run?
Not happening.
You know what? Untie me, and let’s duel, if you dare.
Sure. I’m not scared.
You’re not going to win just because you’re taller!
Although I’m short—
Although… Although I’m short…
Do you think I want to be so short?
Would you like to grow taller?
Yes, yes! I would.
I have a quick fix.
Why isn’t it working?
It’s the wrong hand.
Huh?
Weslie’s hand is mine! Don’t touch it!
Hey, I shower daily! Don’t be so dramatic!
Hurry, run!
One thousand one hundred and eleven,
one thousand one hundred and twelve,
one thousand one hundred and thirteen!
You’re on your way to growing!
Keep it up!
I’m too tired. I can’t jump anymore.
This is what a taller you will look like.
How handsome!
Persistence is key.
This will be you very soon
as long as you keep jumping rope.
Tell me, can you do it?
Yes, I can.
What’s that? I can’t hear you.
Yes, I can!
Wonderful!
We’ll head outside and not bother your training.
Keep it up, Justice Spider!
Okay.
Don’t slow down!
Yes!
Keep it up! Don’t stop!
Ready now?
Bring it on.
I guess it didn’t work.
Can we try something else?
Look over there.
Please, can we try?
Of course.
This is some really sticky fruit sap, huh?
It’ll soften up with a bit more time.
Can we try something else?
No.
Why not?
Yay, my hand is out!
Your hand might be free, but the honey is still on my face.
Come on,
let’s get out of here.
My leg is stuck.
Hang in there, Wolffy!
I’m getting you out!
Yes! The aphid is gone!
Thanks for rescuing me, Weslie.
You’re welcome.
Thanks for helping me open the box, too.
The Energy Seed is mine!
Wait, what?
The other goats’ handprints have expired.
Oh, come on!
Justice Spider?
I’m… over… here!
Two thousand and fifteen,
two thousand and sixteen,
two thousand and seventeen,
two thousand and eighteen,
two thousand and nineteen…
Where are the goats?
Two thousand—
How… How would I know?
I’m busy jumping rope to get taller.
Two thousand and—
Darn it, I forgot how many times I’ve jumped.
Don’t… disturb… me!
It’s no use, Wolffy.
Well, if I have the Energy Seed, I’ll just capture you guys again, anyway.
Come get us, Wolffy!
Watch this.
Sirius!
This is our little “present” for you.
Do you like it, Wolffy?
You can run for all I care.
The Energy Seed is still in my hands, anyway.
Hey, what’s this?
When you were carrying me just now,
I stole it back from you.
I hate you guys!
You’re not going anywhere!
Oh, by the way,
we turned your missiles into boomerangs.
Where’s Wolffy?
A stupid missile is no match for me.
I’m taller! I really am!
Wolffy, Justice Spider, goodbye!
Goodbye! Thank you for your height fix!
END